<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>🌐Wikiyickistan</title>
      <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on 🌐Wikiyickistan</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Welcome to Stickyickistan</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/</guid>
    <description>WARNING FOR PLAYERS I am somewhat trusting you to not meta-game you little rat fucks. There will be information in here that characters do not have. I want to make the world building collaborative, so please use this for reference when creating characters for the setting, and send me your ideas/suggestions for additions/amendments to the world on discord.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>History of Stickyickistan</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Stickyickistan</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Stickyickistan</guid>
    <description>Modern Stickyickistan Welcome to the enchanting realm of Stickyickistan, a captivating City State nestled on an island off the Sword Coast, where an active volcano stands proudly ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Wererats</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Wererats</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Wererats</guid>
    <description>In Stickyickistan there are many nooks and crannies in which Wererats are known to hide, but they mainly reside in the main sewer system beneath the city streets ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Warforged</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Warforged</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Warforged</guid>
    <description>Warforged are a species of construct generally made out of a mix of metals and arcane organic material. This species was originally developed by The Forgewright Guild, and most Warforged in Stickyickistan are still manufactured by them to this day.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mycoforged</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Mycoforged</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Mycoforged</guid>
    <description>This is a fungal horror sub-species of Warforged with several variants that was created by Sibrek Hollowspore of the Zooka Mire Collective.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Halflings</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Halflings</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Halflings</guid>
    <description>Halflings are one of the main species living in the city, and once were the only humanoid creatures on the island. Halflings in Stickyickistan are everywhere and nowhere at once—a people both deeply ingrained in the city-state’s fabric and constantly underestimated.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dwarf</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Dwarf</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Species/Dwarf</guid>
    <description>Dwarves are one of the main species found in the city, but they are a minority. Most dwarves in Stickyickistan come from the Bongstad region, and work as miners in the volcanic rim of Mount Zooka, or as blacksmiths crafting weapons and armor for sale.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Spelljammer</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Spelljammer</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Spelljammer</guid>
    <description>AI Warning lmao Imperial Elven Navy (IEN) – The Space Feds With Pointy Ears The IEN rolls deep like spacefaring feds, rolling up in sleek, magically overpowered ships with the same ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ravnica</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Ravnica</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Ravnica</guid>
    <description>Ravnican Factions Reimagined for Stickyickistan Azorius Senate → Nevercough Tribunal A bureaucratic, law-enforcing body centered in the Capitol building on Nevercough Island ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Eberron</title>
    <link>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Eberron</link>
    <guid>https://chasemilligan.github.io/Wikiyickistan/Sources/Eberron</guid>
    <description>Eberron Factions Reimagined for Stickyickistan The Aurum → The Gilded Nexus A shadowy organization of wealthy merchants, powerful magitech tycoons, and corrupt nobles ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>